Arturo Alejandro Guerra Muñetonez

Email: arturoalejandroguerrma@gmail.com Phone: (57) 310 539 9163

<u>LinkedIn</u> | <u>Portfolio</u> | <u>GitHub</u> Envigado, Colombia

Professional Profile

I am a software developer with knowledge in JavaScript, mongoDB, Express.js, Node.js and React. My previous experience in the field of psychology brings a unique perspective that emphasizes communication and collaboration. This combination enables me to balance technical skills with a user-centered approach, fostering collaborative solutions, and establishing a solid foundation to confidently face unexpected challenges life challenges.

Technical Skills

JavaScript, Python, React, Express.js, MongoDb, Node.js.

Education

2023-2023 Postgraduate Degree in Software Development

UNIMINUTO

2013-2018 Psychology

Pontificia Bolivariana University

2023-2023 Full Stack MERN Developer

Protalento

Work Experience

Feb 2022 - Sep 2022

Lean Solutions Group

Talent Acquisition Analyst

Facilitated the acquisition of human talent through comprehensive personnel search processes and providing robust support in the selection process. My efforts resulted in achieving the highest hiring metric to date in my specific area of responsibility. This strengthened my analytical skills, attention to detail, and organizational abilities.

Feb 2021 - Feb 2022

Pontificia Bolivariana University

Psychologist - University Well-being

As the Coordinator of the Personal Development sub-process and leader of the Addiction Prevention and Space Appropriation area, I was responsible for conceiving and executing proposals and projects aimed at enriching the community's experience. Among my achievements, I successfully organized the first post-lockdown Institutional Well-being event, attracting an audience of over 450 attendees. This experience helped me develop my project management skills and the ability to address crucial issues in real-time.

Additional Information

Other courses: ISO 25000 standard, Introduction to Terminal and Command Line, Basic Programming Course, Introduction to Computational Thinking with Python, Python Fundamentals, Python: PIP and Virtual Environments, Python: Comprehensions, Functions, and Error Handling, Professional Git and GitHub Course.

Languages: Spanish (C2), English (B2)